They sing. They dance. They battle demons.
KPop Demon Hunters is a fantasy, music, comedy film directed by Chris Appelhans.
When K-pop superstars Rumi, Mira and Zoey aren't selling out stadiums, they're using
their secret powers to protect their fans from supernatural threats.
Rumi (voice), played by Arden Cho.
Mira (voice), played by May Hong.
Zoey (voice), played by Ji-young Yoo.
Jinu (voice), played by Ahn Hyo-seop.
Celine (voice), played by Yunjin Kim.
Bobby (voice), played by Ken Jeong.
KPop Demon Hunters is a 2025 American animated musical urban fantasy film
co-written and directed by Maggie Kang and Chris Appelhans.
Produced by Sony Pictures Animation for Netflix, the film stars the voices of Arden Cho, Ahn
Hyo-seop, May Hong, Ji-young Yoo, Yunjin Kim, Daniel Dae Kim, Ken Jeong, and Lee Byung-hun.
The story follows a K-pop girl group, Huntrix, who lead double lives as demon hunters; they face
off against a new rival boy band, the Saja Boys, whose members are secretly demons.
KPop Demon Hunters originated from Kang's desire to create a story inspired by her Korean heritage, drawing on
elements of mythology, demonology, and K-pop to craft a visually distinct and culturally rooted film.
The film was reported to be in production at Sony Pictures Animation by March 2021, with the
full creative team attached, and was animated by Sony Pictures Imageworks.
It was visually influenced by concert lighting, editorial photography, and
music videos; and drew inspiration from anime and Korean dramas.
The soundtrack features original songs by several
musicians, and a score composed by Marcelo Zarvos.
KPop Demon Hunters began streaming on Netflix on June 20, 2025, while a sing-along version of the
film received limited theatrical releases on August 23–24 and October 31 – November 2.
The film received praise for its animation, visual style, voice acting, writing, and music and
became the most-watched original title in Netflix history with over 300 million views.
Its sing-along theatrical release was the widest by number of theaters for a
Netflix film, and the first to top the box office in the United States.
KPop Demon Hunters has garnered numerous accolades, including winning Best Animated Feature and Best Original Song at the 31st Critics'
Choice Awards and 83rd Golden Globe Awards, and being featured in Time magazine as its 2025 Breakthrough of the Year.
The film's soundtrack achieved similar success; it became the first film soundtrack on the Billboard Hot 100 to have four of its songs in the top ten simultaneously, was certified double Platinum by the Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA)
in October 2025, and received five Grammy Award nominations along with a nomination for the Academy Award for Best Original Song (for "Golden") at the 98th Academy Awards; the film itself is also nominated for Best Animated Feature.
A sequel is planned to be released in 2029.
The film explores themes of double life, loyalty,
supernatural, musical, female friendship.
The tone is lighthearted.